Guide to the Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events RG.7.4
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events
1918-2019
New York University Archives
New York University. Office of University Events
New York University. Office of External Affairs. Commencement and Special Events
RG.7.4
44.25 Linear Feet in 42 record carton boxes, 2 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box and 1 half manuscript box
The Commencement and Special Events division was part of the Office of External Affairs and operated under the leadership of the Vice President for External Affairs. In 2002, the Office of External Affairs was replaced by the Office of University Relations and Public Affairs, and the Office of University Events took over the role of event planning. The bulk of the material in this collection documents the planning processes of special events and commencement programs spanning the period 1918-2016.
Conditions Governing Access
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were first accessioned from the Office of External Affairs by the University Archives in 1997. Additional boxes were accessioned from the Office of University Events in 2011. Accretions were transferred to the Archives in 2016, 2018, and 2019.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged topically into three series and chronologically within each series.
Series I. Events
Series II. Publications
Series III. Commencement
Historical Note
The Commencement and Special Events division was part of the Office of External Affairs and operated under the direction of the Vice President for External Affairs. The Commencement and Special Events department was responsible for the planning, organization, and overseeing of university events and commencement ceremonies. Other than convocation ceremonies, the department regularly organized university events such as anniversary celebrations, guest lectures, fundraising dinners, and site dedications. In 2002, the Office of External Affairs was replaced by the Office of University Relations and Public Affairs. The Office of University Events operates within this division and coordinates the many events formerly handled by the Commencement and Special Events department of the Office of External Affairs.
Related Materials
Records of Arthur L. Brandon, 1957-1962
Records of the Office of Radio and Television, 1953-1985
Records of the Office of the Senior Vice President, William F. Payne, for External Affairs, 1968-1980
Scope and Contents
The collection contains files and publications generated by the Commencement and Special Events division of the Office of External Affairs, as well as the Office of University Events. The "Events" series documents the planning process for university events spanning the period 1975-1999. The "Publications" series includes programs from convocations, dedications and other university events spanning the period 1975-1999. The "Commencement" series contains planning materials and publications, including programs, graduation rosters and commencement addresses, from NYU's commencement ceremonies over the period 1918-2019.
Separated Materials
Oversized materials from the NYU Celebrates 2000 event were incorporated into the general University Archives collections for those formats.
Programs (documents); New York (N.Y.).; Correspondence.; Baccalaureate addresses; Universities and Colleges -- Administration; Administrative records.; Commencement ceremonies; New York University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Series I: Events
  - 1982 Parents' Day, Oct 24, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058087 3
  - Nirenberg Reception and Dinner, Oct 6, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Morse Exhibit / Terra Dinner, Sep 14, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Speakers, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academic Convocation (Orientation), Sep 9, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - West Springfield H.S. Visit, May 25, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kriser Seminar Exp., Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kriser Presidential Seminar, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Jose and Miguel de Capriles, Apr 3, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Huntley Lecture, Apr 10, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Chet Huntley Expenses, Mar 10, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hearing on Arts and Education, Mar 5, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 25th Annual Albert Gallatin Assoc. Reception, Oct 26, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Brochures, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Interdepartmental, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Facilities, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Groundbreaking Invitations, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Invitations, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Program, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Remarks by Dr. Brademas, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Coles Center Dedication, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brademas Inauguration Slides, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1981 Parent's Day, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sadat Convocation (1/2), Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Sadat Convocation (2/2), Apr 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Sadat Convocation Press Release and Photographs, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Program of Convocation for Jehan El-Sadat, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Sadat Convocation Mailing Lists, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - List. Greeks, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058086 5
  - Livingston Papers Reception, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Orientation 1980, Apr 22, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Parents' Day 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Parents Day 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Parents' Day Letters General, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Parents' Day Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - WSUC Parents' Day, Nov 18, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - BPA Parents' Day, Dec 9, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - SEHNAP Parents' Day, Dec 9, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Parents' Day Convocation, Fall 1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Parents' Day, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Pit Day Orientatin, Sep 18, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Coles Groundbreaking, Jul 11, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Convocation for Endowed Chairs Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dental Center: Dedication, Sep 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bobst Memorial Service, Sep 13, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Convocation - Parents of Freshmen, Sep 25, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Convocation of James H. Hester, Apr 18, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Graduation Ceremonies Gala, May 28, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Convocation for New Students, Sep 11, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bobst Dedication and Gala - Hester Farewell, May 30, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Convocation for Freshmen, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Development Campaign 1st Year Report (luncheon), Oct 11, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Development Campaign 1st Year Report (Press Conf), Oct 11, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Campaign Announcement (Press Conference & luncheon), Mar 8, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Basketball Celebration, Nov 26, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Library 10th Anniversary (1/2), Oct 25, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bobst Library 10th Anniversary (2/2), Oct 25, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 29, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Convocation, Oct 11, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Convocation A/A orders, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Convocation A.A. Reference, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Convocation Attendance Statistics, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Chet Huntley Lecture, Nov 10, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Gallatin Dinner, Oct 6, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Graduate Student Orientation, Sep 28, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Foundation Executives, Sep 27, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - American Jewish Congress Panel, Sep 18, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Dedication of "Bobcat", Sep 15, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Convocation for Freshmen, Sep 12, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - S.C.E. Fiftieth Anniversary, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058085 7
  - Humanities High School Reception, Jul 25, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Provost's Slideshow / Receptions, Summer 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Up with People, Jun 9, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Abby Weed Grey Publication Dinner, May 9, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tip O'Neill Day, Apr 16, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Kriser Seminar: Joseph Califano, Apr 28, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Giscard D'Estaing Dinner, Apr 27, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Gallatin Fellows Dinner, Apr 21, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Press Conference: Copyright Law, Apr 14, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Oxford - Cambridge Debate, Spring 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Silverstein / Coles P.H. Dinner, Mar 1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Abby Grey Memorial Service, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Emta Faculty Reception, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Badinter Dinner Lecture, Jan 22, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Basketball Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Basketball Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Varsity Basketball Press Conference, Feb 17, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - T.S.O.A. Broadway Opening, Dec 9, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Convocation Procession Reply Cards, Nov 1, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Convocation, Nov 1, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 1982 TSOA Part-time faculty, Nov 19, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Sesquicentennial Calendar / Pin Sales, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Sesquicentennial Poster Sales, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sesquicentennial Calendar Sales, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Sesquicentennial, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Art Exhibitions, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Celebration of the Arts, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - General, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - Interdepartmental, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Humanities Seminars, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Original University Building, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Proclamation Ceremony - City Hall, Oct 13, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Sesquicentennial, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration, Oct 21, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Sesquicentennial Expenses, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Sesquicentennial Sales, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Planning / Proposals for 150th Anniversary, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Winter Celebration, Mar 2, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058084 0
  - SEHNAP: Graphic Arts Tech. Awards, Mar 14, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Albany, NYU Day, Mar 13, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Afternoon at the Square, Mar 10, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Distribution of 1983-1984 Annual Report, Spring 1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - New Exhibits for Snow, Von Guerard, and Pres, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Iakovos, Nov 25, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Reverend Iakovos Convocation, Nov 25, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chet Huntley Lecture, Nov 15, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Third Annual Faculty Convocation, Nov 14, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Gala - Dinner Dance, Nov 3, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - James Burke Dinner, Oct 30, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058083 2
  - Picasso Exhibit Preview / Opening, Oct 25, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 26th Dormitory Dedication, Oct 24, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bowshier Lecture, Reception and Dinner, Oct 22, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Runciman Convocation, Oct 18, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Events of 1984 (1) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Between the Summits Conference, May 2, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - G.P.A. Marnold Lecture, Apr 21, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Inside Story: "The New Spain", Mar 31, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - C.A.S.E. / Postal Rate Commission, Mar 27, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Triangle Fire Commemoration 75th Anniversary, Mar 25, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Young Alumni Event, Mar 22, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gerald Ford Visit to B.P.A., Mar 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Edmund Muskie Visit, Jan 30, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Paul A. McGhee Lecture, Jan 13, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - SEHNAP Puerto Rico Graduation, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Florida Alumni Event, Jan 26, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Campaign Announcement Luncheon, Dec 17, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Chancellor's Holiday Party, Dec 16, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Forman Gymnasium Dedication, Dec 3, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture: Diane Sawyer, Nov 20, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Morse Professorship / Kinnell Publication, Nov 19, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Allen Greenberg Reception, Nov 12, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Gottschalk Convocation, Oct 28, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Professor James Stoker Convocation, Oct 22, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Shimon Peres Honorary Degree, Oct 21, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Peres, Oct 21, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058082 4
  - Petrie Inaugural Lecture, Oct 17, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - T.S.O.A. 20th Anniversary, Oct 15, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Weiner, Kriser Professor, Event, Oct 3, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Fergus G.B. Millar Lecture, Sep 27, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1985 Freshman Convocation, Sep 12, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - C.I.M.S. Robotics Conference, Sep 9, 1984-Nov 1, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Italy: Festival, Jun 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Senior Week: Breakfast, Jun 4, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Trustee Pre-commencement Dinner Program, Jun 4, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Trustee Pre-commencement Dinner Package, Jun 5, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Chancellor's Service Award Ceremony, May 6, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Lena Horne Benefit, Apr 13, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Honorary Degree: Raul Alfonsin, Mar 21, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Alfonsin Convocation, Mar 21, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Winter Celebration, Mar 2, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Onassis Center, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058081 6
  - Hayden Foundation Conference, Fall 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Academic Attire Sale, Fall 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - New Phonathon Center, Aug 26, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Solicitation for Raffle Prizes, Jul 23, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Jerome S. Coles Medal, Fall 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Latin American Conference, Oct 5, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Fix Concert at Coles, Sep 26, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - President's Reception at the Violet, Sep 21, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Recent Alumni Circle Line Trip, Sep 18, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Trustees Pre-commencement Dinner Program, Jun 4, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Third Elmer Holmes Bobst Award, May 19, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Very Special Arts Festival, May 8, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Dormitory & Info Center Dedication Ceremonies, Jun 14, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1987-1988 Alumni Lecture Series (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Spring Celebration 1987, Apr 4, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli Marimo, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Service Awards for 1987, Jun 30, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Onassis Convocation Technical Info, Mar 30, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Onassis Convocation, Mar 30, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Albany: "NYU Day", Mar 9, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Awards / Awards Event Committees, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - President Mario Soares Visit, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Sir Harold Acton Visit, Spring 1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - State Democratic Party Forum, Mar 16, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Postmaster General Dinner, Spring 1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Regional Alumni Activities, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Washington D.C. Alumni Event, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Petrie Lecture, Feb 26, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Florida Alumni Events, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - California Alumni Events, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 1987 Marnold Fellow (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Gallatin Lecture: Kissinger, Dec 1986 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Humanities Council 10th Anniversary, Dec 4, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - G.S.A.S. Centennial, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 1985-86 Faculty Convocation, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1986-87 Recent Alumni Event, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058080 8
  - Chet Huntley Lecture, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tiffany & Co. Anniversary, Fall 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Todman Center Dedication, Oct 30, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Park Bench-Painting, Oct 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NYU Parade, Sep 30, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Plague, Sep 23, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Her Excellency Corazon Aquino Lecture, Sep 19, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Time Lecture: President Aquino, Sep 19, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Chinese University Presidents, Jul 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Liberty Conference, Jul 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - U.A.A. Press Conference, Jun 25, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report Distribution, Summer 1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Leo Jaffe Theatre Dedication, May 21, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Avery Fisher Center Dedication, May 19, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, May 7, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - California Alumni Event, May 4, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - United Staff Association Strike, Aug 29, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058079 0
  - Governor's Forum, Aug 1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Dukakis, Cuomo, et al, Aug 11, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Thomas S. Foley Lecture / Dinner, Jul 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The Creo Society, Inc., May 18, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Belford-Thompson Lecture, May 4, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1988 Spring Celebration, Apr 30, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Spring Celebration, Apr 30, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Heights Lounge / 170 Waverly, Apr 14, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Trustees Pre-commencement Dinner, Jun 11, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Trustees Pre-commencement Dinner Package, Apr 13, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Health Fair / Presidential Forum, Apr 7, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 1988 Washington Square Park Clean Up, Apr 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Chet Huntley Lecture, Mar 10, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial, Mar 10, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Marnold Lecture, Feb 18, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Meeting, Feb 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Palm Beach / Trustees Schedule, Feb 7, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Presidential Lecture Series, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Libraries / Librarians, Dec 15, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Libraries, Dec 15, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Wall Street Premiere, Dec 7, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - N.I.H. Conference, Dec 3, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Kriser School of Dentistry, Nov 18, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Kriser Convocation, Nov 18, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Lee Hamilton Lecture / Dinner, Nov 16, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058078 2
  - Farber / Hughes Dinner, Nov 10, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - All-University Convocation, Oct 22, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - All U Dinner Dance and Convocation, Oct 22, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - All U Dinner Dance and Convocation, Oct 22, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - University Reception and Dinner Dance, Oct 22, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - All U Dinner Dance and Convocation, Oct 22, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - H.E. George Vassilou, Oct 5, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 8th Huntley Memorial Lecture, Sep 27, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - TSOA/TOKYO Presidential Citations, Sep 26, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Wagner Press Conference, Sep 25, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mayoral Debates (Channel 13), Sep 6, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Gift to Washington Square Park, Fall 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - NYU Alumni College (WSUC and Heights), Summer 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Trustee Dinner, May 17, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Trustees Pre-commencement Dinner Package, Mar 22, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - National Education Forum, Apr 28, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Bowsher Luncheon and Seminar, Feb 27, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Robert W. Johnson Grant Press Conference, Feb 2, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Kirball Center for Hebrew and Judaic Studies, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058077 4
  - Dinner: Mr. And Mrs. Leonard N. Stern, Dec 13, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Arthur Carter Hall, Dec 12, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bobst Literary Awards Dinner, Nov 14, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Leonard Stern Events, Fall 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - All U Convocation Dinner-Dance, Oct 20, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - All U Dinner Dance, Oct 20, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Vryonis / Georgakis / Lecture, Oct 10, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Mayor of Athens, Sep 29, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Mitterand Procession Guest List, Sep 28, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - French Revolution Bicentennial, Oct 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Mitterand Convocation, Sep 28, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058076 6
  - Mitterand Guest List, Sep 28, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Fritz, John Honorary Degree, May 9, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - President of Brazil, Spring 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Students' Black Tie Ball, Mar 24, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Violet Ball, Mar 23, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Violet Ball, Mar 24, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Rita Suessmuth Lecture / Dinner, Mar 19, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Andriotti Convocation (1/2), Mar 8, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Fernandez Reception, Feb 28, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - NYU in Albany Day 1990 (1/3) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058075 8
  - NYU in Albany Day 1990 (2/3) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NYU in Albany Day 1990 (3/3) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Resource Network Lunch, Jan 25, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Luncheon in Honor of M. Schwarz, Nov 17, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Wagner Graduate School Dinner, Nov 16, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Dedication, Nov 13, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts and Sciences, Nov 9, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - All U Dinner Dance, Nov 8, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Successful Aging Conference, Nov 1, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Battle for Columbia, Nov 1, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - UAA Dinner, Oct 9, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Carter de Menil Awards, Dec 10, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058074 1
  - Bobst Awards, Dec 4, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - World AIDS Day, Dec 1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Ultra Violet Opening, Jan 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Greeks and the Sea, Nov 1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo Dedication, Nov 13, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo Dedication, Nov 13, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Finance Forum, Nov 10, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture: Rupert Murdoch, Nov 8, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Chet Huntley Lecture, Nov 8, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Music Therapy Clinic: SEHNAP, Oct 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058073 3
  - President Salinas of Mexico Convocation A, Oct 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - President Salinas of Mexico Convocation B, Oct 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SEHNAP Centennial, Oct 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Prime Minister Kaifu of Japan Convocation, Sep 28, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Federation: Keogh Award, Sep 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Patriarch of Constantinople, Jul 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bassists' Convention, Jun 27, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Stern Groundbreaking, Jun 20, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)